<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><testsuite errors="0" failures="1" name="LookUp A Definition" skipped="0" tests="5" time="34.54" timestamp="2021-09-30 08:12:09"><testcase name="Looking up the definition of 'apple'"/><testcase name="Looking up the definition of 'banana'"><failure message="&#10;Expected: a collection containing a string containing &quot;An elongated curved tropical fruit that grows in bunches and has a creamy flesh and a smooth skin&quot;&#10;     but: was &quot;An elongated curved tropical fruit of the banana plant that grows in bunches and has a creamy flesh and a smooth skin.&#10;(Canada, US, Britain, Ireland) Especially, the sweet, yellow fruit of the Cavendish banana cultivar.&quot;, was &quot;(Canada, US, Britain, Ireland) Especially, the sweet, yellow fruit of the Cavendish banana cultivar.&quot;, was &quot;The tropical tree-like plant which bears clusters of bananas. The plant, usually of the genus Musa but sometimes also including plants from Ensete, has large, elongated leaves and is related to the plantain.&quot;, was &quot;(uncountable) A yellow colour, like that of a banana's skin.&#10;banana:  &quot;, was &quot;(mildly derogatory, slang, ethnic slur) A person of Asian descent, especially a Chinese American, who has assimilated into Western culture or married a Caucasian (from the &quot;yellow&quot; outside and &quot;white&quot; inside). Compare coconut (“assimilated Hispanic or Black”) or Oreo (“Black person who is &quot;black outside&quot; and &quot;white inside&quot;”).&quot;, was &quot;(nuclear physics) A banana equivalent dose.&quot;, was &quot;(colloquial) A catamorphism (from the use of banana brackets in the notation).&quot;, was &quot;(slang) The penis. quotations ▼&quot;, was &quot;&quot;, was &quot;&quot;, was &quot;&quot;, was &quot;&quot;, was &quot;(sports) A banana kick.&quot;" type="java.lang.AssertionError">
Expected: a collection containing a string containing "An elongated curved tropical fruit that grows in bunches and has a creamy flesh and a smooth skin"
     but: was "An elongated curved tropical fruit of the banana plant that grows in bunches and has a creamy flesh and a smooth skin.
(Canada, US, Britain, Ireland) Especially, the sweet, yellow fruit of the Cavendish banana cultivar.", was "(Canada, US, Britain, Ireland) Especially, the sweet, yellow fruit of the Cavendish banana cultivar.", was "The tropical tree-like plant which bears clusters of bananas. The plant, usually of the genus Musa but sometimes also including plants from Ensete, has large, elongated leaves and is related to the plantain.", was "(uncountable) A yellow colour, like that of a banana's skin.
banana:  ", was "(mildly derogatory, slang, ethnic slur) A person of Asian descent, especially a Chinese American, who has assimilated into Western culture or married a Caucasian (from the "yellow" outside and "white" inside). Compare coconut (“assimilated Hispanic or Black”) or Oreo (“Black person who is "black outside" and "white inside"”).", was "(nuclear physics) A banana equivalent dose.", was "(colloquial) A catamorphism (from the use of banana brackets in the notation).", was "(slang) The penis. quotations ▼", was "", was "", was "", was "", was "(sports) A banana kick."</failure><system-err>
Expected: a collection containing a string containing "An elongated curved tropical fruit that grows in bunches and has a creamy flesh and a smooth skin"
     but: was "An elongated curved tropical fruit of the banana plant that grows in bunches and has a creamy flesh and a smooth skin.
(Canada, US, Britain, Ireland) Especially, the sweet, yellow fruit of the Cavendish banana cultivar.", was "(Canada, US, Britain, Ireland) Especially, the sweet, yellow fruit of the Cavendish banana cultivar.", was "The tropical tree-like plant which bears clusters of bananas. The plant, usually of the genus Musa but sometimes also including plants from Ensete, has large, elongated leaves and is related to the plantain.", was "(uncountable) A yellow colour, like that of a banana's skin.
banana:  ", was "(mildly derogatory, slang, ethnic slur) A person of Asian descent, especially a Chinese American, who has assimilated into Western culture or married a Caucasian (from the "yellow" outside and "white" inside). Compare coconut (“assimilated Hispanic or Black”) or Oreo (“Black person who is "black outside" and "white inside"”).", was "(nuclear physics) A banana equivalent dose.", was "(colloquial) A catamorphism (from the use of banana brackets in the notation).", was "(slang) The penis. quotations ▼", was "", was "", was "", was "", was "(sports) A banana kick."&#13;
com.gdn.qa.module.ui.test.steps.DefinitionSteps.theyShouldSeeTheDefinitionString(DefinitionSteps.java:38)&#13;
✽.they should see the definition 'An elongated curved tropical fruit that grows in bunches and has a creamy flesh and a smooth skin'(src/test/resources/features/LookUp.feature:14)&#13;
</system-err></testcase><testcase name="Looking up the definition of 'kiwi'"/><testcase name="Looking up the definition of 'mango'"/><testcase name="Looking up the definition of 'pear'"/></testsuite>